

Aika Kreedy

I am energetic ,kind and enjoy working and collaborating with others. Iam Woman in Tech with a background of IT and Business Management . I have Experience in working with the IT industry. Bachelor's science in Computer engineering.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

General

JavaScript Python

Backend

NodeJS ExpressJS REST GraphQL MongoDB/PostgreSQL Ruby on Rails

Frontend

TypeScript
React
Next.js
React Native
Redux
React Query
Webpack
HTML
jQuery
CSS/SASS/styled-components
General
Regex
JavaScript

Tools and technologies

Visual Studio Code
Handlebars/Mustache
Mocha/Jest
Docker
Git+GitHub
GitHub Actions
AWS
Cloud Platforms (MongoDB Atlas,
ElephantSQL, Heroku, Netlify,
Contentful)
TDD
Agile work methods

Links

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aika-k-7 5548246/

https://github.com/aika-kreedy

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Full Stack JavaScript - School of Applied Technology </salt>

September 2022 - December 2022 Intensive three-month training program for full stack web development with a focus on TDD, mob programming, and applied learning.

Post graduate Diploma of Business Management - Punjab Technical University

August 2010 - August 2011

B.Sc Computer Engineering - University
of Basrah

September 2001 - May 2005

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teacher-Assistant-Noblaskolan Saltsjö-Boo.

September 2020 - September 2022

Business Partner-Medical Service Company.

May 2013 - November 2015

Teacher of Computer, Mathematics and Physics

September 2010 - September 2013.

Computer Engineer-Oil Products

Distribution Company.

February 2006 - January 2008
New Life Assistans AB

September 2021 - November 2021

Training for 2 months as a software developer.

Languages

English - Proficient Swedish - Intermediate Arabic - Native